Close

Choose your language

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* Products Featured Developers Product Managers IT professionals Business Teams Leadership Teams
    
    Featured Developers Product Managers IT professionals Business Teams Leadership Teams

    ##### Featured
    
    [
    
    ### Jira
    
    Flexible project management](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira)
    
    [
    
    ### Confluence
    
    Knowledge, all in one place](https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence)
    
    [
    
    ### Jira Service Management
    
    High-velocity service delivery](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira/service-management)
    
    [
    
    ### Trello
    
    Organized & visualized work](https://trello.com/home)
    
    [
    
    ### Rovo NEW
    
    Unlock enterprise knowledge](https://www.atlassian.com/software/rovo)
    
    [
    
    ### Jira Product Discovery NEW
    
    Capture & prioritize ideas](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira/product-discovery)
    
    [
    
    ### Compass NEW
    
    Optimize software health](https://www.atlassian.com/software/compass)
    
    [
    
    ### Guard NEW
    
    Enhanced cloud security](https://www.atlassian.com/software/access)
    
    [
    
    ### Loom NEW
    
    Quick, async video updates](https://loom.com/)
    
    ##### Developers
    
    [
    
    ### Jira
    
    Flexible project management](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira)
    
    [
    
    ### Bitbucket
    
    Collaborative code repos](https://www.atlassian.com/software/bitbucket)
    
    [
    
    ### Compass NEW
    
    Optimize software health](https://www.atlassian.com/software/compass)
    
    ##### Product Managers
    
    [
    
    ### Jira
    
    Flexible project management](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira)
    
    [
    
    ### Confluence
    
    Knowledge, all in one place](https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence)
    
    [
    
    ### Jira Product Discovery NEW
    
    Capture & prioritize ideas](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira/product-discovery)
    
    ##### IT professionals
    
    [
    
    ### Jira Service Management
    
    High-velocity service delivery](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira/service-management)
    
    [
    
    ### Guard NEW
    
    Enhanced cloud security](https://www.atlassian.com/software/access)
    
    ##### Business Teams
    
    [
    
    ### Jira
    
    Flexible project management](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira)
    
    [
    
    ### Confluence
    
    Knowledge, all in one place](https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence)
    
    [
    
    ### Trello
    
    Organized & visualized work](https://trello.com/home)
    
    [
    
    ### Loom NEW
    
    Quick, async video updates](https://loom.com/)
    
    ##### Leadership Teams
    
    [
    
    ### Jira Align
    
    Enterprise strategy alignment](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira/align)
    
    [
    
    ### Jira
    
    Flexible project management](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira)
    
    [
    
    ### Confluence
    
    Knowledge, all in one place](https://loom.com/)
    
    [
    
    ### Loom NEW
    
    Quick, async video updates](https://loom.com/)
    
    Back
    
* Teams
    
    ##### Teams
    
    [
    
    ### Software
    
    Ship high-quality, innovative software faster
    
    ](https://www.atlassian.com/teams/software-development)
    
    [
    
    ### Marketing
    
    Collaborative strategies for marketing success
    
    ](https://www.atlassian.com/teams/marketing)
    
    [
    
    ### IT
    
    Deliver exceptional operations and support services.
    
    ](https://www.atlassian.com/software)
    
    ##### solution

    ##### By team size

    ##### By industry

    Back
    
* Why Atlassian
    
    ##### Why Atlassian
    
    [### Integrations
    
    Connect thousands of apps to your Atlassian products](https://marketplace.atlassian.com/)
    
    [### Customers
    
    Case studies & stories powered by teamwork](https://www.atlassian.com/customers)
    
    [### FEDRamp
    
    Compliant solutions for the public sector](https://www.atlassian.com/trust/compliance/resources/fedramp)
    
    [### Resilience
    
    Enterprise-grade & highly performant infrastructure](https://www.atlassian.com/trust/resilience)
    
    [### Platform
    
    Our deeply integrated, reliable & secure platform](https://www.atlassian.com/platform)
    
    [### Trust center
    
    Ensure your data’s security, compliance & availability](https://www.atlassian.com/trust)
    
    Back
    
* Resources
    
    ##### Resources
    
    [### Customer Support
    
    Ask questions, report bugs & give us feedback](https://support.atlassian.com/)
    
    [### Find Partners
    
    Consulting, training & product customization support](https://partnerdirectory.atlassian.com/)
    
    [### Migration Program
    
    Step-by-step guidance for your Atlassian cloud migration](https://www.atlassian.com/migration)
    
    [### University
    
    Learn and expand your skill set for all things Atlassian](https://university.atlassian.com/)
    
    ##### support

    ##### learn

    Back

* More +
* Less -

Back

* * *

* * *

Privacy Policy
==============

_Effective starting: May 17, 2024_ ([view archived versions](https://www.atlassian.com/legal/archives))

What this policy covers
-----------------------

Your privacy is important to us, and so is being transparent about how we collect, use, and share information about you. This policy is intended to help you understand:

This Privacy Policy covers the information we collect about you when you use our products or services, or otherwise interact with us (for example, by attending our premises or events or by communicating with us), unless a different policy is displayed. For information about how we process applicant and former employee data, please see the [Atlassian Careers Privacy Notice](https://www.atlassian.com/legal/careers-privacy-notice) or the [Former Workplace Privacy Notice](https://www.atlassian.com/legal/formerworkforceprivacynotice). For information about how we process information submitted in a voluntary demographic survey during the application process, see our [Demographic Survey Privacy Notice](https://www.atlassian.com/legal/diversity-survey-privacy-notice). Atlassian, we and us refers to Atlassian Pty Ltd, Atlassian US, Inc. and any of our corporate affiliates. We offer a wide range of products, [including our cloud, server and data center products](https://www.atlassian.com/software).  We refer to all of these products, together with our other services and websites as "Services" in this policy.    

This policy also explains your choices surrounding how we use information about you, which include how you can object to certain uses of information about you and how you can access and update certain information about you.  **If you do not agree with this policy, do not access or use our Services or interact with any other aspect of our business**.  

Where we provide the Services under contract with an organization (for example, your employer), that organization controls the information processed by the Services. For more information, please see Notice to End Users below. This policy does not apply to the extent we process personal information in the role of a processor on behalf of such organizations.

What information we collect about you
-------------------------------------

We collect information about you when you provide it to us, when you use our Services, and when other sources provide it to us, as further described below.  

**Information you provide to us**

We collect information about you when you input it into the Services or otherwise provide it directly to us.    

_**Account and Profile Information:**_ We collect information about you when you register for an account, create or modify your profile, set preferences, sign-up for or make purchases through the Services. For example, you provide your contact information and, in some cases, billing information, when you register for the Services. You also have the option of adding a display name, profile photo, job title, and other details to your profile information to be displayed in our Services.  We keep track of your preferences when you select settings within the Services.

_**Content you provide through our products**_: The Services include the Atlassian products you use, where we collect and store content that you post, send, receive and share. This content includes any information about you that you may choose to include. Examples of content we collect and store include: the summary and description added to a Jira issue, the pages you create in Confluence, the name of a Trello board, your repositories and pull requests in Bitbucket, information regarding an incident in Statuspage or Opsgenie, any stories you name in Jira Align, any forms you create in Jira, and any feedback you provide to us. Content also includes the files and links you upload to the Services. If you use a server or data center version of the Services, we do not host, store, transmit, receive or collect information about you (including your content), except in limited cases, where permitted by your administrator: we collect feedback you provide directly to us through the product and; we collect content using analytics techniques that hash, filter or otherwise scrub the information to exclude information that might identify you or your organization; and we collect clickstream data about how you interact with and use features in the Services. Server and data center administrators can disable our collection of this information from the Services via the administrator settings or prevent this information from being disclosed to us by blocking transmission at the local network level. 

_**Content you provide through our websites:**_ The Services also include our websites owned or operated by us. We collect other content that you submit to these websites, which include social media or social networking websites operated by us. For example, you provide content to us when you provide feedback or when you participate in any interactive features, surveys, contests, promotions, sweepstakes, activities or events.  

_**Information you provide through our support channels:**_ The Services also include our customer support, where you may choose to submit information regarding a problem you are experiencing with a Service.  Whether you designate yourself as a technical contact, open a support ticket, speak to one of our representatives directly or otherwise engage with our support team, you will be asked to provide contact information, a summary of the problem you are experiencing, and any other documentation, screenshots or information that would be helpful in resolving the issue.

_**Payment Information:**_  We collect payment and billing information when you register for certain paid Services.  For example, we ask you to designate a billing representative, including name and contact information, upon registration.  You might also provide payment information, such as payment card details, which we collect via secure payment processing services.

**Information we collect automatically when you use the Services**

We collect information about you when you use our Services, including browsing our websites and taking certain actions within the Services.          

_**Your use of the Services**_: We keep track of certain information about you when you visit and interact with any of our Services. This information includes the features you use; the links you click on; the type, size and filenames of attachments you upload to the Services; search terms; your team’s Jira Align story progress; and how you interact with others on the Services.  We also collect information about the teams and people you work with and how you work with them, like who you collaborate with and communicate with most frequently.  If you use a server or data center version of the Services, the information we collect about your use of the Services is limited to clickstream data about how you interact with and use features in the Services, in addition to content-related information described in "Content you provide through our products," above.  Server and data center administrators can disable our collection of this information from the Services via the administrator settings or prevent this information from being disclosed to us by blocking transmission at the local network level. 

_**Device and Connection Information**_: We collect information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other devices you use to access the Services. This device information includes your connection type and settings when you install, access, update, or use our Services. We also collect information through your device about your operating system, browser type, IP address, URLs of referring/exit pages, device identifiers, and crash data. We use your IP address and/or country preference in order to approximate your location to provide you with a better Service experience.  How much of this information we collect depends on the type and settings of the device you use to access the Services.  Server and data center Service administrators can disable collection of this information via the administrator settings or prevent this information from being disclosed to us by blocking transmission at the local network level.   

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**: Atlassian and our third-party partners, such as our advertising and analytics partners, use cookies and other tracking technologies (e.g., web beacons, device identifiers and pixels) to provide functionality and to recognize you across different Services and devices. For more information, please see our [Cookies and Tracking Notice](https://www.atlassian.com/legal/cookies), which includes information on how to control or opt out of these cookies and tracking technologies. Please refer to [Loom's Cookie Policy](https://www.loom.com/cookie-policy) for details on cookies and tracking technologies used within Loom products and websites.

**Information we receive from other sources**

We receive information about you from other Service users, from third-party services, from our related companies, social media platforms, public databases, and from our business and channel partners. We may combine this information with information we collect through other means described above. This helps us to update and improve our records, identify new customers, create more personalized advertising and suggest services that may be of interest to you. 

_**Other users of the Services**_: Other users of our Services may provide information about you when they submit content through the Services. For example, you may be mentioned in a Jira issue or paged via an Opsgenie incident opened by someone else, a team member may upload content about you to a Trello board, or your team’s story status may be discussed in Jira Align.  We also receive your email address from other Service users when they provide it in order to invite you to the Services.  Similarly, an administrator may provide your contact information when they designate you as the billing or technical contact on your company's account or when they designate you as an administrator. 

_**Other services you link to your account**_: We receive information about you when you or your administrator integrate third-party apps, like Power-UPs, or link a third-party service with our Services. For example, if you create an account or log into the Services using your Google credentials, we receive your name and email address as permitted by your Google profile settings in order to authenticate you. You or your administrator may also integrate our Services with other services you use, such as to allow you to access, store, disclose and edit certain content from a third-party through our Services.  For example, you may authorize our Services to access, display and store files from a third-party document-sharing service within the Services interface. Or you may authorize our Services to connect with a third-party calendaring service or to sync a contact list or address book so that your meetings and connections are available to you through the Services, so you can invite others to collaborate with you on our Services or so your organization can limit access to certain users. Your administrator may also authorize our Services to connect with a third party reporting service so your organization can review how the Services are being used. The information we receive when you link or integrate our Services with a third-party service depends on the settings, permissions and privacy policy controlled by that third-party service. You should always check the privacy settings and notices in these third-party services to understand what data may be disclosed to us or shared with our Services.

_**Atlassian Companies**_:  We receive information about you from other Atlassian corporate affiliates, in accordance with their terms and policies. 

_**Atlassian Partners**_:  We work with a [global network of partners](https://www.atlassian.com/partners) who provide consulting, implementation, training and other services around our products.  Some of these partners also help us to market and promote our Services, generate leads for us, and resell our Services.  We receive information from these partners, such as billing information, billing and technical contact information, company name, what Atlassian Services you have purchased or may be interested in, evaluation information you have provided, what events you have attended, and what country you are in. 

_**Other Partners**_: We receive information about you and your activities on and off the Services from third-party partners, such as advertising and market research partners who provide us with information about your interest in and engagement with, our Services and online advertisements.   

_**Third Party Providers**_: We may receive information about you from third party providers of business information and publicly available sources (like social media platforms), including physical mail addresses, job titles, email addresses, phone numbers, intent data (or user behavior data), IP addresses and social media profiles, for the purposes of targeted advertising of products that may interest you, delivering personalized communications, event promotion, and profiling.

How we use information we collect
---------------------------------

How we use the information we collect depends in part on which Services you use, how you use them, and any preferences you have communicated to us.  Below are the specific purposes for which we use the information we collect about you.

_**To provide the Services and personalize your experience**_: We use information about you to provide the Services to you, including to process transactions with you, authenticate you when you log in, provide customer support, and operate, maintain, and improve the Services.  For example, we use the name and picture you provide in your account to identify you to other Service users. Our Services also include tailored features that personalize your experience, enhance your productivity, and improve your ability to collaborate effectively with others by automatically analyzing the activities of your team to provide search results, activity feeds, notifications, connections and recommendations that are most relevant for you and your team.  For example, we may use your stated job title and activity to return search results we think are relevant to your job function.  We also use information about you to connect you with other team members seeking your subject matter expertise. We may use your email domain to infer your affiliation with a particular organization or industry to personalize the content and experience you receive on our websites. Where you use multiple Services, we combine information about you and your activities to provide an integrated experience, such as to allow you to find information from one Service while searching from another or to present relevant product information as you travel across our websites. Based on your interactions with different Atlassian products and advertisements, we will personalize your experience and tailor our communications and offers to you. To opt out of this personalization, please contact privacy@atlassian.com.  

_**For research and development**_:  We are always looking for ways to make our Services smarter, faster, secure, integrated, and useful.  We use information and collective learnings (including feedback) about how people use our Services to troubleshoot, to identify trends, usage, activity patterns, and areas for integration and to improve our Services and to develop new products, features and technologies that benefit our users and the public. For example, to improve the @mention feature, we automatically analyze recent interactions among users and how often they @mention one another to surface the most relevant connections for users. We automatically analyze and aggregate search terms to improve the accuracy and relevance of suggested topics that auto-populate when you use the search feature. In some cases, we apply these learnings across our Services to improve and develop similar features, to better integrate the Services you use, or to provide you with insights based on how others use our Services. We also test and analyze certain new features with some users before rolling the feature out to all users.  

_**To communicate with you about the Services**_: We use your contact information to send transactional communications via email and within the Services, including confirming your purchases, reminding you of subscription expirations, responding to your comments, questions and requests, providing customer support, and sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and administrative messages.  We send you email notifications when you or others interact with you on the Services, for example, when you are @mentioned on a page or ticket, when a task is assigned to you, or when you are added to a Trello board. Depending on your chosen method of contact, we may send you SMS notifications or call you if you are on-call for incident alerts in Opsgenie. We also provide tailored communications based on your activity and interactions with us.  For example, certain actions you take in the Services may automatically trigger a feature or third-party app suggestion within the Services that would make that task easier.  We also send you communications as you onboard to a particular Service to help you become more proficient in using that Service. These communications are part of the Services and in most cases you cannot opt out of them.  If an opt out is available, you will find that option within the communication itself or in your account settings.   

_**To market, promote and drive engagement with the Services:**_ We use your contact information and information about how you use the Services to send promotional communications that may be of specific interest to you, including by email and by displaying Atlassian ads on other companies' websites and applications.  These communications may be informed by audits of interactions (like counting ad impressions), and are aimed at driving engagement and maximizing what you get out of the Services, including information about new features, survey requests, newsletters, and events we think may be of interest to you.  We also communicate with you about new Services, product offers, promotions, and contests.  You can control whether you receive these communications as described below under "Opt-out of communications."

_**Customer support**_: We use your information to resolve technical issues you encounter, to respond to your requests for assistance, to analyze crash information, and to repair and improve the Services. Where you give us express permission to do so, we disclose information to a third party expert for the purpose of responding to support-related requests.

_**For safety and security**_: We use information about you and your Service use to verify accounts and activity, to detect, prevent, and respond to potential or actual security incidents and to monitor and protect against other malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, including violations of Service policies. 

**_To protect our legitimate business interests and legal rights_:** Where required by law or where we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights, interests and the interests of others, we use information about you in connection with legal claims, compliance, regulatory, and audit functions, and disclosures in connection with the acquisition, merger or sale of a business.  

_**With your consent**_: We use information about you where you have given us consent to do so for a specific purpose not listed above.  For example, we may publish testimonials or featured customer stories to promote the Services, with your permission.    

_**Legal bases for processing (for EEA users)**_: 

If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws.  The legal bases depend on the Services you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your information only where:

* We need it to provide you the Services, including to operate the Services, provide customer support and personalized features and to protect the safety and security of the Services;
* It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Services and to protect our legal rights and interests;
* You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose; or
* We need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place.  Where we are using your information because we or a third party (e.g. your employer) have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Services. 

How we disclose information we collect
--------------------------------------

We make collaboration tools, and we want them to work well for you.  This means disclosing information through the Services and to certain third parties.  We disclose information we collect about you in the ways discussed below, including in connection with possible business transfers. Please note that information about you, your devices, and your behavior collected through third-party cookies, pixels, tags, or other tracking technologies for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising may be considered a “sale” or “share” under certain US state laws. However, Atlassian is not a data broker, and we do not sell personal information for monetary consideration.

**Disclosing to other Service users**

When you use the Services, we disclose certain information about you to other Service users.

_**For collaboration**_: You can create content, which may contain information about you, and grant permission to others to see, disclose, edit, copy and download that content based on settings you or your administrator (if applicable) select.  Some of the collaboration features of the Services display some or all of your profile information to other Service users when you disclose or interact with specific content.  For example, when you comment on a Confluence page or Jira issue, we display your profile picture and name next to your comments so that other users with access to the page or issue understand who made the comment. Similarly, when you publish a Confluence page, your name is displayed as the author of that page, and Service users with permission to view the page can view your profile information as well.  Your team’s story status in Jira Align or certain profile information when you are listed in an Opsgenie on-call schedule, can be seen by other users with certain role permissions or team assignments. Please be aware that some aspects of the Services like Confluence pages, Bitbucket repositories, or Trello boards can be made publicly available, meaning any content posted in that space, including information about you, can be publicly viewed, indexed by, and returned in search results of search engines.  You can confirm whether certain Service properties are publicly visible from within the Services or by contacting the relevant administrator.

_**Managed accounts and administrators**_: If you register or access the Services using an email address with a domain that is owned by your employer or organization or associate that email address with your existing account, and such organization wishes to establish an account or site, certain information about you including your name, profile picture, contact info, content and past use of your account may become accessible to that organization’s administrator and other Service users sharing the same domain.  If you are an administrator for a particular site or group of users within the Services, we may disclose your contact information to current or past Service users, for the purpose of facilitating Service-related requests.   

_**Community Forums**_:  Our websites offer publicly accessible blogs, forums, issue trackers, and wikis (e.g., [Atlassian Community](https://community.atlassian.com/), [Atlassian Developer Community](http://community.developer.atlassian.com/), [Trello Community](https://community.atlassian.com/t5/Trello/ct-p/trello), and [Trello Inspiration](https://trello.com/inspiration)). You should be aware that any information you provide on these websites - including profile information associated with the account you use to post the information - may be read, collected, and used by any member of the public who accesses these websites.  Your posts and certain profile information may remain even after you terminate your account. We urge you to consider the sensitivity of any information you input into these Services. To request removal of your information from publicly accessible websites operated by us, please contact us as provided below. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to and why.

**Disclosing to third parties**

We disclose information to third parties that help us operate, provide, improve, integrate, customize, support and market our Services. Data obtained through the short code program will not be shared with any third parties for their marketing reasons/purposes.

_**Service Providers**_: We work with third-party service providers to provide website and application development, hosting, maintenance, backup, storage, virtual infrastructure, payment processing, analysis, marketing, and other services for us, which may require them to access or use information about you.  If a service provider needs to access information about you to perform services on our behalf, they do so under close instruction from us, including appropriate security and confidentiality procedures designed to protect your information.

_**Atlassian Partners**_: We work with third parties who provide consulting, sales, support, and technical services to deliver and implement customer solutions around the Services. We may disclose your information to these third parties in connection with their services, such as to assist with billing and collections, to provide localized support, and to provide customizations.  We may also disclose information to these third parties where you have agreed to that disclosure.

_**Third Party Apps**_: You, your administrator or other Service users may choose to add new functionality or change the behavior of the Services by installing third party apps within the Services.  Doing so may give third-party apps access to your account and information about you like your name and email address, and any content you choose to use in connection with those apps.  If you are an administrator, or a technical or billing contact listed on an account, we disclose your details to the third-party app provider upon installation. Third-party app policies and procedures are not controlled by us, and this privacy policy does not cover how third-party apps use your information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of third parties before connecting to or using their applications or services to learn more about their privacy and information handling practices. If you object to information about you being disclosed to these third parties, please uninstall the app.

_**Links to Third Party Sites**_: The Services may include links that direct you to other websites or services whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit information to any of those third party sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies, not this one. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

_**Third Party Services:**_ We may offer you the ability to interact with or disclose information to third parties through the Services. For example, we may offer users the ability to log in to the Services via a third-party service like Google, access embedded maps through Google Maps or interact with social media networks via links on the Services. When you intentionally interact with these third parties, we may disclose certain information to those third parties or receive information with those third parties, consistent with your privacy settings on the third-party service. Such information may include contact information, identification, and demographic information, and device information and identifiers. You should always check the privacy settings and notices in these third-party services to understand how those third-parties may use your information.

_**Third Party Widgets**_: Some of our services contain widgets and social media features, such as the Twitter "tweet" button or Facebook "like" button. These widgets and features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the Services, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Widgets and social media features are either hosted by a third-party or hosted directly on our Services. You should always check the privacy settings and notices in these third-party services to understand how those third-parties may use your information.  

_**With your consent**_: We disclose information about you to third parties when you give us consent to do so.  For example, we often display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our public websites. With your consent, we may post your name alongside the testimonial.  

_**Compliance with Enforcement Requests and Applicable Laws; Enforcement of Our Rights**_: In exceptional circumstances, we may disclose information about you to a third party if we believe that sharing is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, including to meet national security requirements, (b) enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service, (c) protect the security or integrity of our products and services, (d) protect Atlassian, our customers or the public from harm or illegal activities, or (e) respond to an emergency which we believe in good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person. For more information on how we respond to government requests, see our [Guidelines for Law Enforcement](https://www.atlassian.com/trust/privacy/guidelines-for-law-enforcement) and our [Transparency Report](https://www.atlassian.com/trust/privacy/transparency-report).

**Disclosing to affiliated companies**

We disclose information we collect to affiliated companies and, in some cases, to prospective affiliates.  Affiliated companies are companies owned or operated by us.  The protections of this privacy policy apply to the information we disclose in these circumstances.

_**Atlassian companies**_: We disclose information we have about you to other Atlassian corporate affiliates in order to operate and improve products and services and to offer other Atlassian affiliated services to you. This includes companies that own or operate the Services.

**_Business Transfers_**: We may disclose or transfer information we collect under this privacy policy in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Services if a transaction takes place, as well as any choices you may have regarding your information.

How we store and secure information we collect
----------------------------------------------

**Information storage and security**

We use industry standard technical and organizational measures to secure the information we store. For more information on where and how we store your information, please see the [Atlassian Trust](https://www.atlassian.com/trust), [Trello Trust](https://trello.com/en-US/trust), and [Jira Align Trust](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira/align/trust) pages. 

While we implement safeguards designed to protect your information, no security system is impenetrable and due to the inherent nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, is absolutely safe from intrusion by others.

If you use our server or data center Services, responsibility for securing storage and access to the information you put into the Services rests with you and not Atlassian. We strongly recommend that server or data center users configure SSL to prevent interception of information transmitted over networks and to restrict access to the databases and other storage points used.

How long we keep information
----------------------------

How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information, as described in further detail below.  After such time, we will either delete or de-identify your information or, if this is not possible (for example, because the information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.  

_**Account information**_: We retain your account information for as long as your account is active and a reasonable period thereafter in case you decide to re-activate the Services.  aWe also retain some of your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements, to support business operations, and to continue to develop and improve our Services. Where we retain information for Service improvement and development, we take steps to eliminate information that directly identifies you, and we only use the information to uncover collective insights about the use of our Services, not to specifically analyze personal characteristics about you.  

_**Information you share on the Services**_: If your account is deactivated or disabled, some of your information and the content you have provided will remain in order to allow your team members or other users to make full use of the Services.  For example, we continue to display messages you sent to the users that received them and continue to display content you provided, but when requested details that can identify you will be removed. 

_**Managed accounts**_: If the Services are made available to you through an organization (e.g., your employer), we retain your information as long as required by the administrator of your account.  For more information, see "Managed accounts and administrators" above.

_**Marketing information**_: If you have elected to receive marketing emails from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time from the date you last expressed interest in our Services, such as when you last opened an email from us or ceased using your Atlassian account.  We retain information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date such information was created.

How to access and control your information
------------------------------------------

You have certain choices available to you when it comes to your information. Below is a summary of those choices, how to exercise them and any limitations.

**Your Choices**: 

Where applicable under local law, you may have certain rights with respect to your personal information.

Depending on which jurisdiction you live in, you may have the right to request information about our processing of your information, to request a copy of your information, to object to our use of your information (including for marketing purposes), to request the deletion or restriction of your information, to request your information in a structured, electronic format, to request to correct or update your information, to request to opt out of “sales” or “sharing” of personal information and targeted advertising (as these terms are defined under applicable law), and to request to opt out of certain profiling activities.  Below, we describe the tools and processes for making these requests.  You can exercise some of the choices by logging into the Services and using settings available within the Services or your account. Where the Services are administered for you by an administrator (see "Notice to End Users" below), you may need to contact your administrator to assist with your requests first.  For all other requests, you may contact us as provided in the Contact Us section below to request assistance.

Your request and choices may be limited in certain cases: for example, if fulfilling your request would reveal information about another person, or if you ask to delete information which we or your administrator are permitted by law or have compelling legitimate interests to keep.  Where you have asked us to disclose data to third parties, for example, by installing third-party apps, you will need to contact those third-party service providers directly to have your information deleted or otherwise restricted.  If you have unresolved concerns, you may have the right to complain to a data protection authority in the country where you live, where you work or where you feel your rights were infringed. Where applicable under local law, you may also contact us as provided in the “Contact Us” section below to appeal any decision we make relating to your request to exercise your rights.

_**Access and update your information**_: Our Services and related documentation (see [Atlassian Documentation](https://support.atlassian.com/atlassian-account/docs/update-your-profile-and-visibility-settings/), [Trello Help](https://support.atlassian.com/trello/docs/my-trello-account/), and [Loom Documentation](https://support.loom.com/hc/en-us/articles/360003473338-How-to-edit-your-personal-account-settings)) give you the ability to access and update certain information about you from within the Service. For example, you can access your profile information from your account and search for content containing information about you using key word searches in the Service.  You can update your profile information within your profile settings and modify content that contains information about you using the editing tools associated with that content.

_**Deactivate your account**_:   If you no longer wish to use our Services, you or your administrator may be able to deactivate your Services account. If you can deactivate your own account, that setting is available to you in your account settings. Otherwise, please contact your administrator. If you are an administrator and are unable to deactivate an account through your administrator settings, please contact the appropriate support team through [Atlassian](https://support.atlassian.com/)’s support pages.  Please be aware that deactivating your account does not delete your information; your information remains visible to other Service users based on your past participation within the Services.  For more information on how to delete your information, see below.  

_**Delete your information**_: Our Services and related documentation (see [Atlassian Documentation](https://confluence.atlassian.com/cloud/delete-a-managed-account-961259516.html), and [Loom Documentation](https://support.loom.com/hc/en-us/articles/360007580997-How-to-leave-and-deactivate-users-from-a-workspace)) give you the ability to delete certain information about you from within the Service. For example, you can remove content that contains information about you using the key word search and editing tools associated with that content, and you can remove certain profile information within your profile settings. Please note, however, that we may need to retain certain information for record keeping purposes, to complete transactions or to comply with our legal obligations.   

_**Request that we stop using your information**_:  In some cases, you may ask us to stop accessing, storing, using and otherwise processing your information where you believe we don't have the appropriate rights to do so.  For example, if you believe a Services account was created for you without your permission or you are no longer an active user, you can request that we delete your account as provided in this policy.  Where you gave us consent to use your information for a limited purpose, you can contact us to withdraw that consent, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place at the time. You can also opt-out of our use of your information for certain marketing purposes by contacting us, as provided below.  When you make such requests, we may need time to investigate and facilitate your request.  If there is delay or dispute as to whether we have the right to continue using your information, we will restrict any further use of your information until the request is honored or the dispute is resolved, provided your administrator does not object (where applicable).  If you object to information about you being disclosed to a third-party app, please disable the app or contact your administrator to do so.

_**Opt out of communications**_: You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by using the unsubscribe link within each email, updating your email preferences within your Service account settings menu, or by contacting us as provided below to have your contact information removed from our promotional email list or registration database.  Even after you opt out from receiving promotional messages from us, you will continue to receive transactional messages from us regarding our Services. You can opt out of some notification messages in your account settings. Please note, you will continue to receive generic ads.

_**Opt out of targeted advertising**_: Where applicable under local law, you may have the right to opt out of targeted advertising by [clicking here](#additional-disclosures-for-ca-residents) and following the instructions. 

You may also be able to opt out of receiving personalized advertisements from other companies who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or who subscribe to the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. For more information about this practice and to understand your options, please visit: [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) and [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

_**Turn off Cookie Controls**_: Relevant browser-based cookie controls are described in our [Cookies & Tracking Notice](https://www.atlassian.com/legal/cookies). Please refer to [Loom’s Cookie Policy](https://www.loom.com/cookie-policy) for details on cookies and tracking technologies used within Loom products and websites.

_**Send "Do Not Track" Signals**_: Some browsers have incorporated "Do Not Track" (DNT) features that can send a signal to the websites you visit indicating you do not wish to be tracked. Our websites may not respond to all browser-based DNT signals; however, our websites do respond to the Global Privacy Control (“GPC”) to opt-out of “sales” of personal information and targeted advertising in certain locales. For more information on the GPC and how to use a browser or browser extension incorporating the GPC signal, see [https://globalprivacycontrol.org/](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/). You can also use the range of other tools we provide to control data collection and use, including the ability to opt out of receiving marketing from us as described above.

_**Data portability**_: Data portability is the ability to obtain some of your information in a format you can move from one service provider to another (for instance, when you transfer your mobile phone number to another carrier).  Depending on the context, this applies to some of your information, but not to all of your information.  Should you request it, we will provide you with an electronic file of your basic account information and the information you create on the spaces under your sole control, like your personal Bitbucket repository.  

How we transfer information we collect internationally
------------------------------------------------------

**International transfers of information we collect**

We collect information globally and may transfer, process, and store your information outside of your country of residence, to wherever we or our third-party service providers operate for the purpose of providing you the Services.  Whenever we transfer your information, we take steps to protect it.  

_**International transfers within the Atlassian Companies**_: To facilitate our global operations, we transfer information globally and allow access to that information from countries in which the Atlassian owned or operated companies have operations for the purposes described in this policy. These countries may not have equivalent privacy and data protection laws to the laws of many of the countries where our customers and users are based. When we disclose information about you within and among Atlassian corporate affiliates, we make use of the Data Privacy Framework to receive personal data transfers from the European Union/European Economic Area to the U.S. (see “Data Privacy Framework Notice” section below), and the standard contractual data protection clauses, which have been approved by the European Commission, to safeguard the transfer of information we collect from the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom (the "UK"), and Switzerland. Refer to [this page](https://www.atlassian.com/legal/data-transfer-impact-assessment) for a list of countries to which we regularly transfer personal data.

_**International transfers to third parties**_: Some of the third parties described in this privacy policy, which provide services to us under contract, are based in other countries that may not have equivalent privacy and data protection laws to the country in which you reside. When we disclose information of customers in the European Economic Area, the UK, or Switzerland, we make use of the European Commission-approved standard contractual data protection clauses, binding corporate rules for transfers to data processors, or other appropriate legal mechanisms to safeguard the transfer.

**Data Privacy Framework Notice**

On July 10, 2023, the European Commission’s adequacy decision for the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF) entered into force.

Atlassian, Inc. and its U.S. subsidiaries (Atlassian Network Service, Inc., Dogwood Labs, Inc., AgileCraft LLC, Halp, Inc., Loom, Inc., Opsgenie, Inc., and Trello, Inc.) adhere to the Data Privacy Framework Principles regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data that is transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the U.S. 

Atlassian complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Atlassian has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union and the United Kingdom in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF.  Atlassian has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF.  If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the DPF Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework Program, please visit the Data Privacy Framework Program website [here](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/). To view Atlassian’s certifications, search for “Atlassian” in the Data Privacy Framework List.

As required under the principles, when we receive information under the Data Privacy Framework and then transfer it to a third-party service provider acting as an agent on our behalf, we have certain liability under the Data Privacy Framework if the agent processes the information in a manner inconsistent with the Data Privacy Framework and we are responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

We encourage you to contact us as provided below should you have a Data Privacy Framework related (or general privacy-related) complaint.  If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our [U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) (free of charge).  Through this third-party dispute resolution provider, we have also committed to cooperating and complying with the information and advice provided by an informal panel of data protection authorities in the European Economic Area, and/or the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (as applicable) in relation to unresolved complaints (as further described in the Data Privacy Framework Principles). You may also contact your local data protection authority within the European Economic Area or Switzerland (as applicable) for unresolved complaints.    

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Data Privacy Framework website](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/), including when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted, you may invoke binding arbitration.  

Atlassian, Inc. is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

Other important privacy information
-----------------------------------

**Notice to End Users**

Many of our products are intended for use by organizations. Where the Services are made available to you through an organization (e.g. your employer), that organization is the administrator of the Services and is responsible for the accounts and/or Service sites over which it has control. If this is the case, please direct your data privacy questions to your administrator, as your use of the Services is subject to that organization's policies. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of an administrator's organization, which may be different than this policy. 

Administrators are able to:

* require you to reset your account password;
* restrict, suspend or terminate your access to the Services;
* access information in and about your account;
* access or retain information stored as part of your account;
* install or uninstall third-party apps or other integrations 

In some cases, administrators can also:

* restrict, suspend or terminate your account access;
* change the email address associated with your account;
* change your information, including profile information;
* restrict your ability to edit, restrict, modify or delete information

Even if the Services are not currently administered to you by an organization, if you are a member of a Trello team administered by an organization, or if you use an email address provided by an organization (such as your work email address) to access the Services, then the owner of the domain associated with your email address (e.g. your employer) may assert administrative control over your account and use of the Services at a later date.  You will be notified if this happens. 

If you do not want an administrator to be able to assert control over your account or use of the Services, you should deactivate your membership with the relevant Trello board, team or enterprise, or use your personal email address to register for or access the Services.  If an administrator has not already asserted control over your account or access to the Services, you can update the email address associated with your account through your account settings in your profile.  Once an administrator asserts control over your account or use of the Services, you will no longer be able to change the email address associated with your account without administrator approval.

Please contact your organization or refer to your administrator’s organizational policies for more information.

Additional disclosures for California residents
-----------------------------------------------

The disclosures in this section apply only to California residents and are intended to supplement the Atlassian Privacy Policy with information required by California law.

The table below describes the categories of personal information we collected in the past 12 months, the purposes for which we may collect and disclose this information, the categories of recipients of disclosures made for business purposes in the past 12 months, and the categories of recipients of disclosures made in the past 12 months that may be considered “sales” of personal information or “sharing” of personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising under California law.

| #### Category of Information | #### Purpose(s) for Collecting & Disclosing | #### Recipients of Disclosures for Business Purposes | #### Recipients of “Sales” or “Sharing” |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Identifiers**, such as name, email address, unique identifiers associated with user or user account, IP Address | Purpose(s) for Collecting & Disclosing<br><br>* Providing the Services<br>* User authentication<br>* Service access controls<br>* Billing<br>* Analytics and research<br>* Marketing<br>* Detecting security incidents<br>* Debugging<br>* Internal research<br>* Service enhancements<br>* Customer support | Recipients of Disclosures for Business Purposes<br><br>* Atlassian Companies<br>* Atlassian Partners<br>* Service Providers<br>* Third Party Apps | Recipients of “Sales” or “Sharing”<br><br>Third Party Advertising Providers |
| **Commercial information**, such as purchase details, transaction records, billing information, billing address, payment card details | Purpose(s) for Collecting & Disclosing<br><br>* Providing the Services<br>* Billing<br>* Analytics and research<br>* Marketing<br>* Detecting security incidents<br>* Debugging<br>* Internal research<br>* Service enhancements<br>* Customer support | Recipients of Disclosures for Business Purposes<br><br>* Atlassian Companies<br>* Atlassian Partners<br>* Service Providers | Recipients of “Sales” or “Sharing”<br><br>\-NA- |
| **Internet or other electronic network activity information**, such as information about your usage of the Services, pseudonymous IDs, clickstream data, device and connection information, browser information, crash data, referring/exit URLs, IP Address | Purpose(s) for Collecting & Disclosing<br><br>* Providing the Services<br>* Internal research<br>* Service enhancements | Recipients of Disclosures for Business Purposes<br><br>* Atlassian Companies<br>* Atlassian Partners<br>* Event Sponsors<br>* Service Providers | Recipients of “Sales” or “Sharing”<br><br>\-NA- |
| **Visual information**, such as photos or avatars, with your consent, recordings of your attendance at our events | Purpose(s) for Collecting & Disclosing<br><br>* Providing the Services<br>* Internal research<br>* Service enhancements | Recipients of Disclosures for Business Purposes<br><br>* Atlassian Companies<br>* Atlassian Partners<br>* Event Sponsors<br>* Service Providers | Recipients of “Sales” or “Sharing”<br><br>\-NA- |
| **Professional or employment information**, such as job title, company name, company domain | Purpose(s) for Collecting & Disclosing<br><br>* Providing the Services<br>* Analytics and research<br>* Marketing<br>* Detecting security incidents<br>* Debugging<br>* Internal research<br>* Service enhancements<br>* Customer support | Recipients of Disclosures for Business Purposes<br><br>* Atlassian Companies<br>* Atlassian Partners<br>* Service Providers | Recipients of “Sales” or “Sharing”<br><br>\-NA- |
| **Geolocation data**, such as your approximate location, IP address, time zone | Purpose(s) for Collecting & Disclosing<br><br>* Providing the Services<br>* Internal research<br>* Service enhancements<br>* Marketing-Customer support | Recipients of Disclosures for Business Purposes<br><br>* Atlassian Companies<br>* Atlassian Partners<br>* Service Providers | Recipients of “Sales” or “Sharing”<br><br>Third Party Advertising Providers |
| **Inferences** (drawn about you based on other personal information we collect), such as preferences, interests, user behavior data | Purpose(s) for Collecting & Disclosing<br><br>* Providing the Services<br>* Internal research<br>* Marketing | Recipients of Disclosures for Business Purposes<br><br>* Atlassian Companies<br>* Service Providers | Recipients of “Sales” or “Sharing”<br><br>Third Party Advertising Providers |
| **Sensitive personal information**, such as login credentials and passwords | Purpose(s) for Collecting & Disclosing<br><br>* User authentication<br>* Service access controls | Recipients of Disclosures for Business Purposes<br><br>* Atlassian Companies<br>* Service Providers | Recipients of “Sales” or “Sharing”<br><br>\-NA- |

If you have questions about the categories of information we may collect about you or the sources of such information, please be sure to visit the section of this policy called, “[What information we collect about you.](#what-information-we-collect-about-you)” For more details about our processing activities, please be sure to visit the section called, “[How we use information we collect.](#how-we-use-information-we-collect)” And for more information about how we may disclose information to third parties, please visit the section called, “[How we disclose information we collect.](#how-we-disclose-information-we-collect)” 

**_Sensitive personal information:_** We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information for purposes other than permitted under applicable law.

**_Retention_**: We retain your personal information for as long as necessary to carry out the business purposes described in this policy, or as otherwise required under law. The length of retention may vary depending upon factors such as recordkeeping or legal compliance requirements, the need to resolve inquiries or complaints, and the existence of an ongoing relationship with you. Please visit the “[How long we keep information](#how-long-we-keep-information)” section of this privacy policy for more information about specific retention criteria for different categories of personal information.

_**Exercising your rights**_: If you are a California resident, there are some additional rights that may be available to you under the California Consumer Protection Act (“CCPA”). This policy explains the tools that we have made available to you to exercise your data rights under the CCPA, including such as the rights to request information about how we process your personal information, request deletion and the right to request access to the specific pieces of categories of personal information we have collected about you.

For more information on how to exercise these your rights, please visit the “[How to access and control your information](#how-to-access-and-control-your-information)” section of this policy. We encourage you to manage your information, and to make use of the privacy controls we have included in our Services. You will not be discriminated against for exercising any of your privacy rights under the CCPA. In order to protect your information from unauthorized access or deletion, we may require you to provide additional information to for verification your identity. If we cannot verify your identity, we will not be able to fulfill your requests to know, access provide, correct, or delete your information.

_**Opt out of certain disclosures to third parties**_: You may also opt out of “sales” of personal information and “sharing” of personal information for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising by clicking here and following the instructions. Where required, we also honor requests to opt out submitted via privacy preference signals recognized under applicable law, such as the Global Privacy Control (“GPC”). For more information on the GPC and how to use a browser or browser extension incorporating the GPC signal, see [https://globalprivacycontrol.org/](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/). We do not knowingly sell or share the personal information of consumers under 16 years of age.

_**Authorized agent**_: You may also authorize an agent to exercise your rights on your behalf. To do this, you must provide the authorized agent with written permission to exercise your rights on your behalf, and we may request a copy of this written permission from the agent when they make a request on your behalf. We may also ask you to verify your own identity and directly confirm with you that you have granted permission to the authorized agent. 

**Our policy towards children**

The Services are not directed to individuals under 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact the appropriate support team (see [Atlassian](https://support.atlassian.com/), [Jira Align](https://help.jiraalign.com/hc/en-us/requests/new), or [Trello](https://trello.com/contact) support pages). 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by adding a notice on the Services homepages, login screens, or by sending you an email notification. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.  We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use the Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

If you disagree with any changes to this privacy policy, you will need to stop using the Services and deactivate your account(s), as outlined above.

**Contact Us**

Your information is controlled by Atlassian Pty Ltd and Atlassian, Inc.  If you have questions or concerns about how your information is handled, please direct your inquiry to Atlassian Pty Ltd, which we have appointed to be responsible for facilitating such inquiries or, if you are a resident of the European Economic Area, please contact our EU Representative.

Atlassian Pty Ltd  
c/o Atlassian, Inc.  
350 Bush Street, Floor 13  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
E-Mail: [privacy@atlassian.com](mailto:privacy@atlassian.com)

EU Representative:

Atlassian B.V.  
c/o Atlassian, Inc.  
350 Bush Street, Floor 13  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
E-Mail: [eudatarep@atlassian.com](mailto:privacy@atlassian.com)

UK Representative:

Atlassian (UK) Operations Limited  
c/o Herbert Smith Freehills LLP  
Exchange House  
Primrose Street  
London EC2A 2EG  
United Kingdom  
E-Mail: [ukrepresentative@atlassian.com](mailto:ukrepresentative@atlassian.com)

Key Changes
-----------

**Effective May 17, 2024**

We have updated the section Data Privacy Framework Notice as part of our Data Privacy Framework certification.

**Effective April 1, 2024**

We have incorporated Loom into the Privacy Policy.  
  
**Effective July 17, 2023**

We have replaced the section **Privacy Shield Notice** with **EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Notice** to reflect the European Commission’s adequacy decision for the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (DPF) on July 10, 2023.

**Effective January 1, 2020**

We have updated the **Other important privacy information** section by adding a section on the California Consumer Privacy Act.

**November 1, 2019**

* We are updating our Privacy Policy to reflect Jira Align and Trello specific examples as we fully integrate them into the Atlassian family.  
* We added details on data we may collect from third parties and public databases.
* We provided information about how we create user profiles and how you can opt out of this.

November 1, 2018

* We are updating our Privacy Policy to reflect the expansion of our cloud data storage infrastructure

May 25, 2018

* Better navigation and user-friendly language. To make the policy easier to understand, we use clear, plain language and examples that illustrate our activities. We reformatted our privacy policy page with active links, so you can quickly find the information that matters most to you.  
* How we integrate our products. We're always improving our products to give you a frictionless and customized experience. The updates to our policy describe the tools we’ve built to make our products smarter and allow you to move seamlessly from one Atlassian product to another.
* More control over your information. We make it easy for you to control the information you provide to us. Our policy explains how you can make choices about your information, and the measures we’ve put in place to keep your information secure.
* Using our products for work. Many users have access to our services through their organizations (e.g., their employers), who control their accounts or use of our services. The updated policy clarifies our relationship to these users and explains the tools available to administrators of these users. 

* * *

Related content
---------------

#### Former Workplace Privacy Notice

#### Careers Privacy Notice

#### Diversity Survey Privacy Notice

#### Cookies & Tracking Notice

Stay informed
-------------

Subscribe to receive notifications from us about updates to our legal terms (including our legal policies) and our list of sub-processors.

##### products

##### Resources

##### Learn

Copyright © 2024 Atlassian

Choose language Deutsch English Español Français Italiano 한국어 Magyar Nederlands 日本語 Polski Português русский 中文
